Ta-dah!
Do I look terrifying?
Oh! You're so adorable, it's terrifying!
It looks perfect on you, Doux!
I'm gonna wear it tomorrow
at the Face Reveal Ceremony.
I am the demon king's daughter, Doux!
Fear me!
Eek! How spooky!
N-No...
I wanted Lady Doux to have an outfit
that'd make her look
terrifying and dignified...
Vouche!
IN CHARGE OF THE OUTFIT
VOUCHE
THE FACE REVEAL CEREMONY IS TOO LIVELY!!
"The Face Reveal Ceremony Is Too Lively!!"
Are you okay?
Do I look okay?
All that happens at a Face Reveal Ceremony
is literally her showing her
face and greeting the crowd.
It's not that simple!
The Face Reveal Ceremony determines
if the next demon king is truly worthy
of their position and our service!
That's what's determined there!
And if they aren't, some
have even plotted mutinies
and assassinations!
Lady Doux doesn't even know
how to be a proper demon yet
so what do you think will happen?!
Yeah, but she's not going
to learn that by tomorrow.
Just give up and deal with it.
No, there's still a way.
What's that?
This is the speech manuscript I spent
all night writing for Lady Doux!
Oh, that's what you meant.
If I let Lady Doux handle
her own speech, it'd be...
When Doux grows up,
Doux wants to go on field
trips with everyone,
make a pool made of sweets,
lay in the sun with Papa,
have sports festivals, and sing songs!
That's how that'd go.
She wouldn't utter a single word
befitting of the next demon king!
You stayed up all night,
and it messed with your head.
In order to make sure tomorrow's ceremony
doesn't fail, I need to get this to her!
Pardon me.
Lady Doux.
I must talk to you about
tomorrow's ceremony.
Lady Doux seems more serious than usual.
What is she doing?
This is... could it be
a speech manuscript?!
I had no idea she was writing one herself.
I'll just have to take it and
swap it out with the one I wrote.
But she's working so hard on writing
it, so I shouldn't take it...
But then again...
Big Sister?
Y-Yes?
What are you doing?
Er, uh!
Um... Y-You look so serious writing
that, so I was just curious...
Doux is writing all the stuff she's
gonna say at the recital tomorrow.
O-Oh, I see.
It's not a recital! And now it's becoming
even more difficult to swap out!
Hm?
A diary about me?
BIG SISTER JAHI DIARY!!
WE DID A STEALING TRIAL TODAY!
We did a stealing trial today!
I BROUGHT HIM MUSHROOMS!
I brought him mushrooms!
Big Sister taught me
magic, and we played lots!
BIG SISTER TAUGHT ME MAGIC AND WE PLAYED LOTS!
Big Sister.
I-I'm terribly sorry, Lady Doux!
I read that without permission!
It's okay!
I've been writing in that diary
ever since I met you, Big Sister.
Huh?
I've been writing in it so I
don't forget all the things you
taught me and can learn them!
So, see?
I can draw magic circles
without looking now!
I kept working real hard,
and now I learned how!
I'll do my best tomorrow,
so just watch me, okay?
Lady Doux...
We will now start the
Face Reveal Ceremony.
Wait patiently to see and hear the words
of Lady Doux, our next demon king!
It's finally time, Dahaka.
It is, darling.
Oh, just look how magnificent she looks.
It's finally begun!
What? You're still worried?
Actually, I'm the most anxious right now.
And I never got to give
her the manuscript.
But!
I have no regrets.
All that's left is for me to
believe and watch over her.
I am the demon king's daughter, Doux!
Ooh!
Everyone!
Um... Um...
Uh... Hm?
What was I supposed to say again?
Good morning!
That's definitely a greeting
only Doux could do!
How lovely.
Doux!
"Doux's Dream."
"When Doux grows up, Doux
wants to conquer the world!"
Huh?!
D-Did Lady Doux actually just
say "conquer the world"?
"Because Papa told me that
conquering the world is amazing
and we'll make everyone
in the world friends!"
Uh?
"But I need to become a full-fledged
demon to do that, so Doux is studying!
And so I'm gonna show everyone!"
Sorry.
Please make some space.
Please make some space!
Doux, we're ready!
Thanks!
Okay, then...
Just watch!
Huh?
Th-That spell is...
Boom!
That's...
TREE
The spell I taught her...
You've grown so much, Doux...
Y-Your Majesty?!
Do you remember, Jahi?
The first time you and Doux met...
When Doux could barely even walk.
You're doing amazing, Doux!
So this is Your Majesty's...
Hm, looks like you will also suffice
as the next demon king's attendant.
Huh?! B-But that's so sudden!
What's the problem with that?
You've gotten used to being
my attendant, haven't you?
I want you to support
Doux as she grows, Jahi.
Support her...
That's right...
At some point, I was
concentrating so much
on teaching
that I had forgotten...
I did it! I did it!
Yay!
Lady Doux is growing at her
own pace, as she should.
And that my other duty is to
support her growth by her side.
She taught me lots of things I
couldn't do. So I learned them,
and now I can do lots of things.
That's wonderful, Lady Doux.
And when Doux conquers the world...
Doux is going to teach everyone around
the world things they can't do!
Doux is gonna conquer the world
to help everyone who's in trouble.
Wha?!
You pulled that off brilliantly, Doux!
I'm so proud of you, Doux!
How?!
She ruined everything with that last part!
You can only conquer the world
by taking from others, oppressing
them, and ruling over them!
And yet Lady Doux...
Don't be such a spoilsport.
Just look at that crowd
and how excited they are!
Everyone is admiring how brave Doux looks.
She couldn't possibly
be any more successful.
B-But...
You need to be more honest with yourself.
You just praised her a moment ago,
saying, "That's wonderful, Lady Doux."
Wha—
And while you were beaming.
Really?!
I-I-I...
I take back what I said!
Please don't get a big head over this!
Just because you grew a tiny bit
doesn't change the fact that
I have many things
I need to teach you still!
So...
I hope you'll continue to
be prepared, Lady Doux!
Yup!
The demon world.
A chaotic world where all demons
carry out all their evil deeds.
With his great power, the demon king
set out to conquer all worlds.
But...
The demon king suddenly
stopped his conquest,
letting a fleeting moment of
peace to come to the world.
And the reason behind this decision...
There are only a few who
know that the reason
lies within the demon king's daughter.
The heir to the demon king...
Her name is Doux.
So what about Doux made the evil demon
king stop his plans to conquer the world?
Ow!
The reason...
Ah! Welcome home, Papa!
Oh, Doux!
Were you a naughty little girl?
I'll help you carry your stuff, 'kay?
Y-You're such a sweet child that
cares so much for your father!
The reason he stopped his conquest is...
The Future Demon King Is Too Kind!!
THE FUTURE DEMON KING IS TOO KIND!!
Oh, darling.
Are you already done
with work for the day?
No, he is not.
He said he wanted to play with Lady
Doux and ran out of the office.
Oh, dear...
So, Dahaka, what did you
and Doux play today?
Well, we actually weren't playing.
Doux said she wanted to study.
Study?
I wanted to study spwells!
What's wrong? Are you tired of your toys?
Nuh-uh.
Well, I promised everyone at my recital!
I want to be a great demon
king like you, Papa!
Doux...
You're not only kind,
but you've grown so much!
I'm learning real hard! Just watch!
Um...
Ubaaborunikka Tajaruuya Koyanyo!
This incantation! It's a
language conversion spell?!
Is she trying to learn
such a high-level spell?!
Rumu...ri... Rumu...to ...ta...
This is where I always get stuck...
Doux! You're amazing!
You were able to recite a
long incantation this far!
Yes! That's already amazing.
It's hopeless.
Ever since the Face Reveal
Ceremony ended in a huge success,
His Majesty and Lady Dahaka are
babying Lady Doux even more.
Jahi, I've made up my mind!
Huh?! A-About what?
Since Doux has made significant progress
in becoming the next demon king,
her trial today will be to experience
the demon king's duties!
Duties!
What?!
Hmph. I'll acknowledge the guts you had
to sneak into the demon castle as spies.
Get moving!
You rebels!
On your knees!
Your Majesty, please
punish these criminals.
Harrumph!
Hey! What's Lady Doux doing here?
His Majesty apparently wanted her
to experience his duties
to help her become the next demon king.
What the hell?!
As she said, my daughter Doux
will be punishing you all today.
Yup!
What?!
Tch! Who do you think we are?
What could a little brat like her do?
We'll make you pay!
This feels so comfy and nice.
Sleepy bye.
Sh-She put them to bed?!
This is supposed to be a
spell called Dark Spores
which rots away anything it touches but...
Lady Doux, what is this?!
Well, all of the prisoners are always
sleeping on top of really hard rocks,
so I learned a spell to
make really fluffy futons.
I see...
This is quite a brilliant spell itself.
I need you to at least try
to scold her, Your Majesty!
STRATEGY MEETING
I won't accept this!
I had handled the southern expedition
field mission up until now!
Well, I was put in charge of
it because you're useless.
The weaker they are, the louder they cry!
What?! Say that again!
Hey, stop that! All of you!
When it gets this bad, the only
way to shut them up is with force.
Bring it on! Step outside!
Have some tea.
Thank you...
What a gentle flavor...
They calmed down somehow!
You work so hard, Doux.
Thank you, Doux.
It's very delicious.
Yup!
Okay, let us continue the meeting.
Regarding the various supplies needed
on these expedition field missions...
Is there anything else that you need
other than what's already been discussed?
Yes!
Huh?! Uh, well, if you
would then, Lady Doux...
How many snacks can they take with them?
They can't bring any!
But if they're going on field trips,
it'd be more fun to bring snacks.
They're not field trips! They're
expedition field missions!
Why don't we just make them field trips?
Yes, let's.
That's that.
No!
I knew this would happen.
Lady Doux's kindness makes everyone
else around her kind and easygoing.
Yay!
And it's unstoppable.
There's trouble, Your Majesty!
This is the ends of the demon
world, the Jet Black Forest.
JET BLACK FOREST
The child of... a giant?
Yes.
He can't understand our words,
so even when we try to move
him, he just won't budge.
The giants are great warriors,
members of an ancient civilization,
and are known for their
unparalleled strength.
That's not surprising.
But the bigger problem
here is not their strength
but the fact that he
doesn't understand us.
My language conversion spell doesn't
work on the giants' language.
Then maybe if we use a
little bit of force...
What just...
What?!
Lady Doux!
It's okay.
The giant quieted down.
Papa! I'll try that talky spell!
Er, Doux. That spell
doesn't work on giants...
But...
Doux wants to try!
Very well. Give it a try.
'Kay!
Your Majesty?
Let's believe in Doux's growth.
Ubaabarunikka Tajaruiya Koyanru...
Rumuri... Rumuto... Iru... Iru...
Um, uh...
Ah!
Irupapitto!
This is...
Ah, the spell is weak, but the
range is quite impressive.
This should...
I guess it didn't work after all.
Hm?
Lady Doux, what are you....
Mr. Lady Bug!
Er... Lady Doux! Now's not
the time for catching bugs!
That child is lost.
And the bug spoke!
This child was separated from the
giants and got lost in the forest
while the giants were moving.
I know because I was stuck on him.
Doux, is this...
Well, if the spell doesn't work on giants,
I thought I'd have everyone
around here help!
If he's lost, let's all
look for his parents!
I-I see...
Er, who exactly is "everyone"?
That giant came from the northeast.
Whoa!
N-N-Now a tree's talking!
Hey.
And even the mushrooms!
Wh-What in the world is going on?
Perhaps Doux's kindness and
the fact that she knows
she's going to be the next
demon king made this happen.
This is truly a method befitting Doux.
Befitting Lady Doux...
Mr. Lady Bug! Mr. Tree! Thank you!
Don't worry about it.
No problem.
Let's go, Mr. Giant.
We're all together, so it's okay!
Bye-bye!
We made new friends again.
Yes.
His Majesty is staying behind
at their settlement
to work out an alliance with the giants.
I'm sure that Lady Doux's kindness will
continue to affect those around her.
Demons do not need kindness.
At least, that's what I
thought until recently.
But now, there's a small part of
me that wants to see just how much
Lady Doux's kindness can change the world.
Did you have fun again today?
Today was fun!
I'm glad to hear that.
Big Sister Jahi! Let's do another
trial together tomorrow!
Yes, of course.
I am your attendant, after all.
"LET'S READ THE PICTURE BOOK"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: NAOKI YANAGISAWA
SONG: DOUX
Teach me, teach me even more
Cruel and inhumane things!
Cruel and inhumane.
These trials are super duper fun
Doux can, Doux can do them all
Steal all the mushrooms
Must shrewdly oppress!
Let's play and share everything!
No sharing allowed!
Let's take someone we don't know
And become friends
You just know
So many things
Please teach me, please teach me
Big Sister Jahi
O Great Benevolent God,
Lord Ahura Mazda...
What did you just say?
The kindness and innocence
that child possesses...
I fear the future where the
demons use it for evil.
She should not be in the demon world.
Bring her to heaven.
This child...
The daughter of the demon king, Doux.